Life hurts. Love heals.
Bravetown is a drama, music film directed by Daniel Duran.
After an accidental drug overdose, a talented teenage DJ goes to live with his estranged father in a
small Army town, where he gets to the bottom of his own pain and learns empathy for others.
Alex, played by Josh Duhamel.
Martha, played by Maria Bello.
Annie, played by Laura Dern.
Kerry, played by Katrina Norman.
Josh Harvest, played by Lucas Till.
Jim, played by Tom Everett Scott.
Bravetown is a 2015 American independent musical drama film written by Oscar Orlando
Torres, and was directed by Daniel Duran in his directorial debut.
The film stars Lucas Till, Josh Duhamel and Kherington Payne.
The film was released in a limited release and through video on
demand on May 8, 2015, by Entertainment One.
The film explores themes of dance, small town, parent
child relationship, grief, us military.
The tone is emotional.